John Idoko

Front-End Software Engineer

CONTACT

idokojohn42@yahoo.com

+2347036060982

Benue Nigeria

linkedin.com/in/ john-idoko-474251218

github.com/KhengJohn

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science(Ed)
Biology
Benue State University
2017 - Present

SKILLS

LANGUAGES

HyperText Markup Langage (HTML)

Cascading Style Sheet (CSS)

JavaScript (JS)

LIBRARIES

React jQuery Nodejs

FRAMEWORKS

Bootstrap TailwindCSS

TOOLS

GitHub, Netlify, Wix, Heroku

DESIGN

Photoshop, Corel draw, Sketch, Figma

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A web developer who is solution oriented, with proven experience in implementing user-friendly and responsive (mobile first approach). Passionate about driving innovation and developmentthrough technology. Capable of learning and adapting to new work environment while sharing my experience to ensure maximum user efficiency.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Engineer

MinervaHub

October 2021 - Present | REMOTE

- * Developed UI and implemented fully responsive and user friendly web applications
- * Write performant, morden and robust code for diverse arrays of clients abd for internal company projects.
- * commucating and collaborating with multi-disciplinary teams of engineers, designers, producers, clients and stakeholders on daily basis.

Front-End Developer

Oche'Nehi

March 2021 - August 2021 | Makurdi

- * Collaborated with a small team of student designers and developers to spread a new brand.
- * Developed and maintained code for in-house and client websites

Team Manager

Kaafila

December 2021 - March 2022 | REMOTE

* Managed a team of traders for a blockchain company

Front-End Developer

UpWork

July 2019 - September 2021 | REMOTE

- * Converted UI Designs to live web pages
- * Implemented websites from conception to deployment

OTHER SKILLS

UI Design Graphic Design Data Entry Video Editing